{
    "subject": "resource/Sara_Guasch",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Chile",
    "human_readable": "Sara Guasch was born in Chile.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9658877849578857,
            "question": "How might having been born in Chile have influenced Sara Guasch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9482516646385193,
            "question": "Is Sara Guasch originally from Chile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.884126603603363,
            "question": "Where was Sara Guasch born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7731088399887085,
            "question": "Does Sara Guasch still live in Chile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6774389743804932,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Sara Guasch's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6587837934494019,
            "question": "What country is Sara Guasch from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5565792322158813,
            "question": "What are some cultural aspects of Chile that Sara Guasch might be familiar with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5102325081825256,
            "question": "Where might Sara Guasch have spent her childhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39278775453567505,
            "question": "What is known about Sara Guasch's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23343239724636078,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Chile?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sara Guasch was born in Chile.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3434_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Sara Guasch's early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3434_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might Sara Guasch have spent her childhood?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3434_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some cultural aspects of Chile that Sara Guasch might be familiar with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3434_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3434_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3434_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3434_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3434_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3434_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3434_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3434_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3434_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3434_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3434_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that Sara Guasch was born in Valparaiso, Chile. Therefore, the statement \"Sara Guasch was born in Chile\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}